MOHAMMAD AYAZ

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER

Contact



North Nazimabad



03142354714



mohammadayazsheikh@gmail.com



https://mohammadayazsheikh.github.io



https://github.com/MohammadAyazSheikh



https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-ayaz-870ba4205/



https://www.fiverr.com/mohammad_ayaz

☼ Skills

React Native



Express.js



Mongodb



Javascript



Typescript



React.js



Ionic/Angular.js



Docker





About Me

I enjoy making user interface for mobile apps. I have experience in developing Cross-Platform mobile apps. I want to be a part of an organization where I can devote myself fully and joyfully give out best of my talents and skills to become its stronger asset seeks to apply for the position of React Native Developer.

Education

Bachelors In Computer Science

PAF-KEIT (2023)

Work Experience

Freelancer

May 2021 - 2022

React Native Developer

Fugen Services

April 2022 - 2024

Software Engineer

Gridizen

April 2024 - Present

Software Engineer

Projects

- Itmenaan.pk
- Educode Academy
- TheCut
- Gridizen
- Alomdah.sa
- Pickup Pals
- Fugen POS
- Voitz